[
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.2169,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob009.pddl",
    "runtime": 50.89142394065857
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0989,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob019.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.22589063644409
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0759,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob015.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.29802894592285
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.4723,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob012.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.21845293045044
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0332,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob004.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.757219552993774
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0866,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob024.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.0069215297699
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0832,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob010.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.512616872787476
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 4,
    "p_success": 0.1702,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob014.pddl",
    "runtime": 56.863744497299194
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 22,
    "p_success": 0.8827,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob021.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.21308898925781
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 21,
    "p_success": 0.8486,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob011.pddl",
    "runtime": 56.76153111457825
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 6,
    "p_success": 0.4958,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob002.pddl",
    "runtime": 59.68020987510681
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.7014,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob006.pddl",
    "runtime": 59.503663063049316
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 13,
    "p_success": 0.6428,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob016.pddl",
    "runtime": 60.4064519405365
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.5129,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob022.pddl",
    "runtime": 60.3151273727417
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.2343,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob017.pddl",
    "runtime": 60.43151307106018
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.2045,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob003.pddl",
    "runtime": 62.52291393280029
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0269,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob020.pddl",
    "runtime": 65.42295575141907
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 6,
    "p_success": 0.5042,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob013.pddl",
    "runtime": 69.0287299156189
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 93,
    "p_success": 0.7431,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob001.pddl",
    "runtime": 58.51637029647827
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0129,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob005.pddl",
    "runtime": 74.51819157600403
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.4333,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob023.pddl",
    "runtime": 86.84938478469849
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.2546,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob018.pddl",
    "runtime": 88.03991985321045
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.3165,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob007.pddl",
    "runtime": 91.43284726142883
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.1465,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob008.pddl",
    "runtime": 94.05766606330872
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0817,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob027.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.45819449424744
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 15,
    "p_success": 0.9981,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob026.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.206244707107544
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0987,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob030.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.490588426589966
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0455,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob029.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.37394690513611
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 12,
    "p_success": 0.294,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob028.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.51791977882385
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.2407,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob034.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.29063558578491
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob040.pddl",
    "runtime": 50.58559489250183
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 16,
    "p_success": 0.4999,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob031.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.78159022331238
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0545,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob039.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.68789744377136
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.3323,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob037.pddl",
    "runtime": 54.35409188270569
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 11,
    "p_success": 0.2832,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob032.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.17214894294739
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 18,
    "p_success": 0.3828,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob036.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.40315103530884
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.3025,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob038.pddl",
    "runtime": 61.40147352218628
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0983,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob043.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.38847351074219
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1101,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob044.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.44363021850586
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0565,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob035.pddl",
    "runtime": 69.60579490661621
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.175,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob033.pddl",
    "runtime": 70.44075679779053
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.3414,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob041.pddl",
    "runtime": 62.665724992752075
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob045.pddl",
    "runtime": 50.87618398666382
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0375,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob025.pddl",
    "runtime": 93.92700719833374
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 12,
    "p_success": 0.2279,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob047.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.556267976760864
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 13,
    "p_success": 0.2658,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob046.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.46421694755554
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0788,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob049.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.92351675033569
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.3071,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob042.pddl",
    "runtime": 90.41235494613647
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.06,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob050.pddl",
    "runtime": 55.0437388420105
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 15,
    "p_success": 0.7463,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob051.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.96690249443054
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0693,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob053.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.052594900131226
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob055.pddl",
    "runtime": 50.82004690170288
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 12,
    "p_success": 0.4004,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob052.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.826788902282715
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0647,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob054.pddl",
    "runtime": 56.137685775756836
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.2825,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob058.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.474528789520264
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.2633,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob057.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.52038526535034
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 27,
    "p_success": 0.704,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob056.pddl",
    "runtime": 57.457048177719116
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 4,
    "p_success": 0.241,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob048.pddl",
    "runtime": 83.02362298965454
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob065.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.14580965042114
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0632,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob063.pddl",
    "runtime": 55.951717138290405
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0391,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob060.pddl",
    "runtime": 63.847750663757324
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0665,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob059.pddl",
    "runtime": 70.11795711517334
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 44,
    "p_success": 0.7145,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob061.pddl",
    "runtime": 60.77591013908386
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 18,
    "p_success": 0.2644,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob064.pddl",
    "runtime": 62.23849940299988
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1535,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob068.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.484323263168335
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob070.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.2152955532074
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.6801,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob066.pddl",
    "runtime": 69.42344689369202
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.2106,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob062.pddl",
    "runtime": 78.0099356174469
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.0927,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob067.pddl",
    "runtime": 67.54203128814697
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.2813,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob073.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.88533091545105
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob075.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.223323345184326
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 14,
    "p_success": 0.7728,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob071.pddl",
    "runtime": 55.28585457801819
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1345,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob077.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.82962894439697
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob080.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.188977003097534
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob074.pddl",
    "runtime": 63.59477519989014
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.02,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob069.pddl",
    "runtime": 78.04507946968079
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 37,
    "p_success": 0.6959,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob076.pddl",
    "runtime": 60.35876798629761
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1351,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob082.pddl",
    "runtime": 52.55475091934204
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0291,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob079.pddl",
    "runtime": 61.65682029724121
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob084.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.464261531829834
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0979,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob083.pddl",
    "runtime": 56.22472310066223
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 6,
    "p_success": 0.869,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob081.pddl",
    "runtime": 63.06228852272034
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0657,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob085.pddl",
    "runtime": 63.89901852607727
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob090.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.45509672164917
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 24,
    "p_success": 0.6376,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob087.pddl",
    "runtime": 56.6271333694458
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.765,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob072.pddl",
    "runtime": 91.9757661819458
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0774,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob088.pddl",
    "runtime": 54.32830286026001
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 37,
    "p_success": 0.7167,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob086.pddl",
    "runtime": 59.71196269989014
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.4101,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob078.pddl",
    "runtime": 92.80544638633728
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob095.pddl",
    "runtime": 51.54123377799988
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 13,
    "p_success": 0.8566,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob092.pddl",
    "runtime": 59.714773416519165
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 8,
    "p_success": 0.6783,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob091.pddl",
    "runtime": 61.63535952568054
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 4,
    "p_success": 0.333,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob093.pddl",
    "runtime": 68.14337921142578
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0705,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob097.pddl",
    "runtime": 53.94436168670654
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.5221,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob096.pddl",
    "runtime": 59.74106025695801
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0271,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob089.pddl",
    "runtime": 79.62976098060608
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.2825,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob098.pddl",
    "runtime": 61.51783061027527
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0566,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob094.pddl",
    "runtime": 73.00037407875061
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0526,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob099.pddl",
    "runtime": 63.00783157348633
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0346,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob100.pddl",
    "runtime": 95.35843396186829
  }
]